dignaruto.com 2008-09-21

# Privacy Policy | Watch Naruto Episodes Online

**Legal Disclaimer:**

Trademarks belong to their respective owners. http://www.dignaruto.com/ or any representative of this domain does not host or upload any video content.

**DigNaruto.Com Privacy Statement**

What follows is the Privacy Statement for the domain DigNaruto.com

**Email Addresses**

We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t send advertising via email.

**Ownership of Information**

DigNaruro.com is the sole owner of any information collected on the domain.

**Comments**

The user comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion.

**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. DigNaruto.com does not have access to this data.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but DigNaruto.com may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If DigNaruto.com is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

DigNaruto.com websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by DigNaruto.com

**Notification of Changes**

When DigNaruto.com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using the contact form.
